const QUESTIONS_MOCK = {
  response_code: 0,
  results: [
    {
      category: "CATEGORY0",
      type: "TYPE0",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY0",
      question: "QUESTION0",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER0",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER0",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER0",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER0",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY1",
      type: "TYPE1",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY1",
      question: "QUESTION1",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER1",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER1",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER1",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER1",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY2",
      type: "TYPE2",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY2",
      question: "QUESTION2",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER2",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER2",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER2",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER2",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY3",
      type: "TYPE3",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY3",
      question: "QUESTION3",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER3",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER3",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER3",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER3",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY4",
      type: "TYPE4",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY4",
      question: "QUESTION4",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER4",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER4",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER4",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER4",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY5",
      type: "TYPE5",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY5",
      question: "QUESTION5",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER5",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER5",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER5",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER5",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY6",
      type: "TYPE6",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY6",
      question: "QUESTION6",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER6",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER6",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER6",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER6",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY7",
      type: "TYPE7",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY7",
      question: "QUESTION7",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER7",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER7",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER7",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER7",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY8",
      type: "TYPE8",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY8",
      question: "QUESTION8",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER8",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER8",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER8",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER8",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY9",
      type: "TYPE9",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY9",
      question: "QUESTION9",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER9",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER9",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER9",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER9",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY10",
      type: "TYPE10",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY10",
      question: "QUESTION10",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER10",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER10",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER10",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER10",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "CATEGORY11",
      type: "TYPE11",
      difficulty: "DIFFICULTY11",
      question: "QUESTION11",
      correct_answer: "CORRECT_ANSWER11",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER11",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER11",
        "INCORRECT_ANSWER11",
      ],
    },
  ],
};

export default QUESTIONS_MOCK;
